Phillip Navarrete

Computer Scientist

Personal Info

Address:

5 Mayford Way,

CO16 8XN

Phone:

+44 7708 787541

E-mail:

phillipvictor2000@gmail.com

Programming Languages (Proficient)

SQL

Python

PHP

C, C++

Programming Languages (Familiar)

HTML/ CSS

Java/ Kotlin

JavaScript, JQuery

Business Skills

Leadership

Project Management

Delegation

Hard Skills

Programming Logic
Problem Solving
Data Structures

I am a hard-working individual with a specialist skillset that is suitable for this job; including, but not limited to: problem decomposition, time managent and abstract thinking. I hope to gain experience in the field of Computer Science, more specifically in programming, to improve my knowledge.

Experience

2018-11 - **Freelance**

Present Backend Web Developer

Created multiple backend interfaces for wordpress

hosted sites using PHP, SQL and JQuery.

• Communicated with clients to meet specification.

2016-09 - Snappy Snaps Clacton

2019-12 IT Technician

- · Headed the maintenance of 5+ machines.
- Built and installed new computer systems.

Education

2019-09 - University of Loughborough

Present

Computer Science BSc.

· Achieved a 95% in Functional Programming, 87% in Web Programming, and 92% in Object Orientated Programming with an overall average (including other modules) of 79.3%

2017-09 - Colchester Sixth Form College

2019-06

4 A-Levels & AS-Level in Further Maths.

- · Maths A, Computing B, Chemistry B, Physics C
- · Further Maths B
- · Mentored a first year student in Maths whilst completing A-Levels.

Projects

Online Calendar

- · Built and hosted an Online Calendar app on Amazon's AWS Cloud9
- · App uses PHP, MySQL and JQuery.

FTS: Faster Than Sound

• Designed single-player roguelike strategy game using p5.js (a JavaScript library).

Library Management System

- · Built a working book management system that could be implemented at a Library.
- · Wrote the software for the system in Python.